[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Pacific Ocean is the largest of the Earths oceanic divisions. Its name is derived from the Latin name Mare Pacificum which has the following meaning.", "correct_answer": "The Peaceful Sea", "incorrect_answers": ["The Lonely Sea", "The Smooth Sea", "The Lonely Sea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of actors did director James Cameron intend to cast for the 1986 science fiction movie Aliens?", "correct_answer": "Actors with American accents", "incorrect_answers": ["Actors with unusual face features", "African American actors", "Tall actors"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How would you say What is your name? in Tagalog?", "correct_answer": "Ano ang pangalan mo?", "incorrect_answers": ["Ilang taong gulang ka na?", "Ano ang ginagawa mo?", "Saan ka nakatira?"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of meal is the Norwegian Omelette?", "correct_answer": "Dessert", "incorrect_answers": ["Drink", "Salad", "Soup"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Sun is a main sequence star and as such generates energy by this process, joining hydrogen nuclei together into helium.", "correct_answer": "nuclear fusion", "incorrect_answers": ["nuclear spallation", "isomerisation", "induced gamma emission"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I shall call him squishy and he shall be mine and he shall be my squishy. is a quote from what Disney animated film?", "correct_answer": "Finding Nemo", "incorrect_answers": ["Pocahontas", "The Fox and the Hound", "A Bugs Life"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the end of Back to the Future Part III, is time travel possible?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what two years did Vivienne Westwood receive the British Designer of the Year award?", "correct_answer": "1990 and 1991", "incorrect_answers": ["2001 and 2002", "1996 and 1997", "1994 and 1995"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The turtle-dove is closely related to the raven.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In three of these countries corruption is widely spread. Which is the odd country?", "correct_answer": "Iceland", "incorrect_answers": ["Romania", "Russia", "Ukraine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What American female singer and actress makes a brief appearance in the 1999 comedy American Pie?", "correct_answer": "Christina Milian", "incorrect_answers": ["Fergie", "Mariah Carey", "Cassie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which section of Israel is Eilat located?", "correct_answer": "South", "incorrect_answers": ["East", "West", "North"]}]